KAINAT FAYYAZ

CREATIVE DESIGNER

Phone - +92 306 7420188

Email - kainatfayyaz12@gmail.com

Address - Sabzazar H Block

Profile

Strong desire to join a progressive organization that gives me scope to develop and update my knowledge and skills. I am a forward-looking individual, having good communication skills and managing abilities. I try to learn something new from every experience good or bad because I believe there is always room for self-improvement both personally and professionally

Education

2021 - CONTINUE

Bechelors in Computer Science (BSCS) Virtual University of Pakistan

2015 - 2017

Intermediate, (I.C.S)
BISE Lahore

2013 - 2015

Matriculations, (Computer Science)
BISE Lahore

Skills

- Logo Design
- Picture Editing
- Infographics
- Banners
- Flyer
- SQA
- Vector Tracing
- Social Media Creatives
- Web Graphics
- Branding

Work Experience

Graphic Designer + SQA

Apr 2021 - Present

Perception IT

I'am working there as a SQA in manual testing on responsive and web. Also working with the resposibilities of creative department

Sales Executive

2019 - Mar 2021

1.5 years of experience in Call Centre, Silk bank

Certificate

Graphic Design

Feb 2022 Opus Solution

I've done my certificate in Graphic Design from Opus Solutions

Android Development

2018 - 2019 UET Lahore

I have done my certificate PSDF Course of 6 months duration in android Development from KICS, UET Lahore

Expertise











Language

- English
- Urdu
- Punjabi